export const Data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    type: 'normal',
    question:
      " Q1. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book. ",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    type: 'multiline',
    question:
      " Q2 .Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    type: 'multiChoise',
    question:
      "Q3 .Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    options: [
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test1',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test2',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test3',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test4',
        },
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    type: 'normal',
    question:
      " Q4. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book. ",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    type: 'multiline',
    question:
      " Q5 .Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    type: 'multiChoise',
    question:
      "Q6 .Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    options: [
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'testing1',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'testing2',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'testing3',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'testing4',
        },
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    type: 'normal',
    question:
      " Q7. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book. ",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    type: 'multiline',
    question:
      " Q8 .Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    type: 'multiChoise',
    question:
      "Q9 .Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    options: [
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test1',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test2',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test3',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test4',
        },
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    type: 'checkbox',
    question:
      "Q10 .Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    options: [
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test11',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test12',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test13',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'test14',
        },
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    type: 'multicheckbox',
    question:
      "Q11 .Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    options: [
      {
        answer: 'test111',
        id: 111,
        status: false,
      },
      {
        answer: 'test122',
        id: 122,
        status: false,
      },
      {
        answer: 'test133',
        id: 133,
        status: false,
      },
      {
        answer: 'test144',
        id: 144,
        status: false,
      },
      {
        answer: 'test155',
        id: 155,
        status: false,
      },
      {
        answer: 'test166',
        id: 166,
        status: false,
      },
      {
        answer: 'test177',
        id: 177,
        status: false,
      },
      {
        answer: 'test188',
        id: 188,
        status: false,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    type: 'radiobutton',
    question:
      "Q12 .Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.",
    options: [
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'radio1',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'radio2',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'radio3',
        },
      },
      {
        option: {
          answer: 'radio4',
        },
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    type: 'multiimage',
    question:
      " Q13. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book. ",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    type: 'image',
    question:
      " Q14. Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book. ",
  },
];
